http://www.azcommerce.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Menu
If you visit our site to read or download information, such as consumer brochures or press releases:
We collect and store information related to the name of the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, length of your visit to the site, various pages, and other statistical information associated with your visit. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
If you identify yourself by sending an email or joining our email circulation list(s):
We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide such information to us.
If you decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message requesting assistance or information or by joining our email circulation list(s), we will use this information in various ways and the material you submit may be seen by various people. We may enter it into our computer system to share with various divisions of the Arizona Commerce Authority.
All electronic communications with our organization, including email, may constitute a “record” pursuant to Arizona law and may be subject to disclosure. Also, email is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is very sensitive, or includes personal information, you might want to send it by postal mail instead.
Except as may be required by law, we will not sell any personally identifying information to any party, nor will we provide it to any party for sale or commercial purposes. The Arizona Public Records law and other state and federal statutes may, under certain circumstances, require the disclosure of such information, including the provision of the information for commercial purposes.
×
Move Left
Move Right
